Guide to the UTU Records
UTU Records
- System Team Captains on CSX Transportation (Box 79, Folder 26)
- (Box 79, Folder 27)
- New and Notices (Box 80, Folder 1)
- Misc. Correspondence (Box 80, Folder 2)
- Sec. 6 Notices (Box 80, Folder 3)
- Wage-Rules Movement (Box 80, Folder 4)
- Organizing the Trucking Industry (Box 80, Folder 5)
- "The Potential for a Labor-Management Partnership" (Box 80, Folder 6)
- Deregulation and Industrial Relations (Box 80, Folder 7)
- Villanova Law School's Center for Continuing Education (Box 80, Folder 8)
- Labor and the Changing Economy (Box 80, Folder 9)
- Cliff Merritt Books (Box 80, Folder 10)
- "People Helping People" (Box 80, Folder 11)
- "The Human Side of Railroading" (Box 80, Folder 12)
- Index (Box 80, Folder 13)
- Milwaukee Road Sprint Trains (Box 80, Folder 14)
- Before the Committee on Commerce, Science and Transportation of the United States Senate (Box 80, Folder 15)
- "Economic Advantages of Transporting Coal by Rail" vs. "Coal Slurry Pipeline" (Box 80, Folder 16)
- "Economic Advantages of Transporting Coal by Rail" vs. "Coal Slurry Pipeline" (Box 80, Folder 17)
- "Transportation and Energy" (Box 80, Folder 18)
- "Transportation and Energy" (Box 80, Folder 19)
- Local 1221's Formal Appeal of Formal General Chairperson (Box 80, Folder 20)
- Rule G (Box 80, Folder 21)
- Milwaukee Road (Box 80, Folder 22)
- "Background" Vol. 23 (Box 80, Folder 23)
- Meeting Logs (Box 80, Folder 24)
- UTU Research and Schedule Department Directory (Box 80, Folder 25)
- National Railway Labor Conference (Box 80, Folder 26)
- "Strength in Brotherhood: The Story of the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen" (Box 81, Folder 1)
- "Strength in Brotherhood: The Story of the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen" (Box 81, Folder 2)
- "Abridge Decimal Classification Dewey" (Box 81, Folder 3)
- "Westward to Promontory" (Box 81, Folder 4)
- (Box 81, Folder 5)
- News and Declarations (Box 82, Folder 1)
- Chesser on Project 70 (Box 82, Folder 2)
- Commercial Drivers License Program (Box 82, Folder 3)
- "Background" Vol. 22 (Box 82, Folder 4)
- The United Transportation Union's Selective Strike Technique (Box 82, Folder 5)
- Correspondence (Box 82, Folder 6)
- Agreements (Box 82, Folder 7)
- "Background" Vol. 13 (Box 82, Folder 8)
- March 4, 1981 Agreement (Box 82, Folder 9)
- Amtrak Employee Assistance Program (Box 82, Folder 10)
- Report and Recommendations of the UTU Study Commission Established by the Signatory Parties to the October 15, 1982 Agreement (Box 82, Folder 11)
- Exhibits to UTU Submission on Crew Consist Part I (Box 82, Folder 12)
- Exhibits to UTU Submission on Crew Consist Part II (Box 82, Folder 13)
- Exhibits to UTU Submission on Crew Consist Part III (Box 82, Folder 14)
- Scott Harvey (Box 82, Folder 15)
- Conrail- Tips Program (Box 82, Folder 16)
- SP- Santa Fe Merger (Box 82, Folder 17)
- "Operation: Red Block Case Study" (Box 82, Folder 18)
- Merger Proposal (Box 82, Folder 19)
- Merger Proposal (Box 82, Folder 20)
- Vandalism (Box 83, Folder 1)
- The New England Economy and the Boston and Maine Railroad System (Box 83, Folder 2)
- Some Analysis of Railroad Data (Box 83, Folder 3)
- A Brief Review of Various Network Models (Box 83, Folder 4)
- Reliability in Railroad Operations (Box 83, Folder 5)
- Railroad Reliability and Freight Car Utilization: An Introduction (Box 83, Folder 6)
- SBA No. 18 Decisions (Box 83, Folder 7)
- Rail Trip Time Reliability: Evaluation of Performance Measures and Analysis of Trip Time Data (Box 83, Folder 8)
- Determinants of Line Haul Reliability (Box 83, Folder 9)
- The Impact of Classification Yard Performance on Rail Trip Time Reliability (Box 83, Folder 10)
- Models for Investigating Rail Trip Time Reliability (Box 83, Folder 11)
- Reliability in Railroad Operations: Executive Summary (Box 83, Folder 12)
- Improving Railroad Reliability: A Case Study of the Southern Railway (Box 83, Folder 13)
- Improving Railroad Reliability: A Case Study of the Southern Railway Executive Summary (Box 83, Folder 14)
- Procedures for Improving Railroad Reliability (Box 83, Folder 15)
- Costing in Railroad Operations: A Proposed Methodology (Box 83, Folder 16)
- Reliability in Railroad Operations- Studies in Railroad Operations and Economics (Box 83, Folder 17)
- Reliability in Railroad Operations: Executive Summary (Box 83, Folder 18)
- Vandalism Suppression by Helicopter (Box 83, Folder 19)
- Railroad Engineman Task and Skill Study, 1972 (Box 83, Folder 20)
- The New England Economy and the Boston and Maine Railroad System (Box 83, Folder 21)
- Regional Rail Planning- Fall Seminars 1976 (Box 83, Folder 22)
- A Curricular of Study for Professional Practitioners (Box 83, Folder 23)
- Correspondence (Box 83, Folder 24)
- Testimony of James R. Snyder (Box 83, Folder 25)
- Appendix D: Technical Issues (Box 83, Folder 26)
- Federal Register- Part II Department of Transportation (Box 83, Folder 27)
- Summary of Railroad Accidents/ Incidents (Box 83, Folder 28)
- Employee Assistance Program (Box 83, Folder 29)
- 1990 Annual Program Evaluation (Box 83, Folder 30)
- Railroad Freight Car Requirements fro Transporting Energy, 1974-1985 (Box 83, Folder 31)
- Reliability in Railroad Operations: Executive Summary (Box 83, Folder 32)
- Biological Rhythms (Box 83, Folder 33)
- CSX (Box 83, Folder 34)
- News Letters/ Clippings (Box 83, Folder 35)
- Field Manual- Control of Alcohol and Drug Use in Railroad Operations (Box 83, Folder 36)
- Locomotive Engineers Journal (Box 83, Folder 37)
- Proceedings of the Joint Conference on Alcohol Abuse and Alcoholism, 1972 (Box 83, Folder 38)
- National Institute on Drug Abuse Research Monograph Series (Box 83, Folder 39)
- Bethlehem Steel Railroads (Box 83, Folder 40)
- Alcoholism Program CN Railroad (Box 83, Folder 41)
- Alcoholism- Burlington Northern (Box 83, Folder 42)
- The Economic Impact of Rail Service in New England (Box 83, Folder 43)
- Proposed Qualification Requirements fro Selected Railroad Jobs (Box 83, Folder 44)
- "Transportation and Energy" (Box 83, Folder 45)
- (Box 83, Folder 46)
- Economic Advantages of Transporting Coal by Rail vs. Coal Slurry Pipeline (Box 83, Folder 47)
- "One Direction: Forward, One Future: Solid, Choose UTU" (Box 83, Folder 48)
- "One Direction: Forward, One Future: Solid, Choose UTU" (Box 83, Folder 49)
- "One Direction: Forward, One Future: Solid, Choose UTU" (Box 83, Folder 50)
- "One Direction: Forward, One Future: Solid, Choose UTU" (Box 83, Folder 51)
- Problem Drinking Among Railroad Workers- Extent, Impact, and Solutions (Box 83, Folder 52)
- Problem Drinking Among Railroad Workers- Extent, Impact, and Solutions (Box 83, Folder 53)
- National Fraternal Congress of America: 93rd Annual (Box 83, Folder 54)
- National Fraternal Congress of America: 94th Annual (Box 83, Folder 55)
- National Fraternal Congress of America: 85th Annual (Box 83, Folder 56)
- Transportation and Energy (Box 83, Folder 57)
- Economic Advantages of Transporting Coal by Rail vs. Coal Slurry Pipeline (Box 83, Folder 58)
- Constitution and General Rules of the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen (Box 83, Folder 59)
- Operation Stop: Third Annual Chairpersons Conference, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 1)
- United Transportation Union Research and Statistical Department Telephone Directory (Box 84, Folder 2)
- EAP Activity Report (Box 84, Folder 3)
- Newsletters (Box 84, Folder 4)
- Unification Agreement and Constitution- United Transportation Union (Box 84, Folder 5)
- Unification Agreement and Constitution- United Transportation Union (Box 84, Folder 6)
- Unification Agreement and Constitution- United Transportation Union (Box 84, Folder 7)
- Clinchfield- TP-MP Term: R Cases (Box 84, Folder 8)
- Central of Georgia (Box 84, Folder 9)
- Kyle- ICG (Box 84, Folder 10)
- Organizing- Engine Service (Box 84, Folder 11)
- Hardin's Letter- Organizing (Box 84, Folder 12)
- BLE- Organizing (Box 84, Folder 13)
- Organizing 80-20 Letter (Box 84, Folder 14)
- Teamster (Box 84, Folder 15)
- Organizer (Box 84, Folder 16)
- R+D (Box 84, Folder 17)
- 1979 UTU Convention (Box 84, Folder 18)
- Consolidation Report (Box 84, Folder 19)
- Report of the Committee on Constitution (Box 84, Folder 20)
- "Crossties Through Carolina" (Box 84, Folder 21)
- Convention (Box 84, Folder 22)
- Report of the Committee on Constitution, 1983 (Box 84, Folder 23)
- "Progress Through Unity" (Box 84, Folder 24)
- (Box 84, Folder 25)
- (Box 85, Folder 1)
- Index to General Chairmen's Reports (Box 86, Folder 1)
- Index to General Chairmen's Reports (Box 86, Folder 2)
- Index to General Chairmen's Reports (Box 86, Folder 3)
- Index to General Chairmen's Reports (Box 86, Folder 4)
- Index to General Chairmen's Reports (Box 86, Folder 5)
- Index to General Chairmen's Reports (Box 86, Folder 6)
- Index to General Chairmen's Reports (Box 86, Folder 7)
- (Box 86, Folder 8)
- Trackage Agreements (Box 87, Folder 1)
- Watergate (Box 87, Folder 2)
- 1990 Report (Box 87, Folder 3)
- "The Human Side of Railroading" (Box 87, Folder 4)
- "Alternatives in the World of Work" (Box 87, Folder 5)
- "Recent Initiatives in Labor-Management Cooperation" (Box 87, Folder 6)
- "A Plant-Wide Productivity Plan in Action: Three Years of Experience with the Scanlon Plan" (Box 87, Folder 7)
- Ohio Association of Railroad Passengers (Box 87, Folder 8)
- Awards (Box 87, Folder 9)
- Association of American Railroads (Box 87, Folder 10)
- Audited Financial Statements and Other Financial Information (Box 87, Folder 11)
- CSX Transportation Random Drug Testing Program as required by Federal Railroad Administration (Box 87, Folder 12)
- 1990 Directory- International Headquarters and Locals (Box 87, Folder 13)
- "Background" Vol. 23 (Box 87, Folder 14)
- "Background" Vol. 23 (Box 87, Folder 15)
- "Background" Vol. 23 (Box 87, Folder 16)
- "Background" Vol. 23 (Box 87, Folder 17)
- "Background" Vol. 23 (Box 87, Folder 18)
- Intermodal Demonstration Phase II (Box 87, Folder 19)
- Emergency Board Report #178 (Box 87, Folder 20)
- Your Union Dues (Box 87, Folder 21)
- Levinon Railroads Sec. 6 Notices (Box 87, Folder 22)
- Reaching the Union Members (Box 87, Folder 23)
- It Costs Money to Run a Union (Box 87, Folder 24)
- Protection of RR Employees in Consolidations (Box 87, Folder 25)
- Collins (Box 87, Folder 26)
- P.C. Trustee Baker on Northeast (Box 87, Folder 27)
- Program: Transportation Seminar (Box 87, Folder 28)
- "Report of the General Secretary and Treasurer- 1990" (Box 87, Folder 29)
- Railroad of the Professionals: Rail Lingo (Box 87, Folder 30)
- DOT Coleman- Nat'l Trains Policy (Box 87, Folder 31)
- "Labor-Management Alcoholism Journal" (Box 87, Folder 32)
- "Changes in Full Crew Law" (Box 87, Folder 33)
- "American Productivity Center" (Box 87, Folder 34)
- Constitution and By-Laws (Box 87, Folder 35)
- "Problem Drinking Among Railroad Workers" (Box 87, Folder 36)
- Statewide Master Plan for Transportation in New York (Box 87, Folder 37)
- TTT Institute of Transportation, Travel and Tourism (Box 87, Folder 38)
- News Clippings and Articles (Box 87, Folder 39)
- Correspondence (Box 87, Folder 40)
- Memorandums (Box 87, Folder 41)
- Hours of Service Act as Amended by Public Law 91-169 (Box 87, Folder 42)
- Federal Railroad Safety Act of 1970 (Box 87, Folder 43)
- Drug Use and Testing (Box 87, Folder 44)
- Insurance and Benefits (Box 87, Folder 45)
- Manual of Wages and Working Conditions Applicable to International Employees of the United Transportation Union (Box 87, Folder 46)
- Statewide Master Plan for Transportation in New York (Box 87, Folder 47)
- The Ladies Auxiliaries to the Railroad Brotherhoods (Box 87, Folder 48)
- Conrail Employment Trends (Box 87, Folder 49)
- Organizing (Box 88, Folder 1)
- Kyle- Kansas (Box 88, Folder 2)
- Kyle- Kansas (Box 88, Folder 3)
- Chicago, Missouri and Western (Box 88, Folder 4)
- Gulf- Mississippi (Box 88, Folder 5)
- Short Lines (Box 88, Folder 6)
- Alcohol Rules (Box 88, Folder 7)
- Dakota Minn-East (Box 88, Folder 8)
- Long Island (Box 88, Folder 9)
- FRA Rules (Box 88, Folder 10)
- Drug Laws (Box 88, Folder 11)
- Proposed FRA Random Testing Rules (Box 88, Folder 12)
- Random Drug Testing (Box 88, Folder 13)
- Random Testing Bill (Box 89, Folder 1)
- Proposed Alcohol Rules-1984 (Box 89, Folder 2)
- "Proposal to Provide Financing Services to Ohio High Speed Rail Task Force" (Box 89, Folder 3)
- Ohio High Speed Rail Task Force (Box 89, Folder 4)
- Department of Transportation Federal Railroad Administration (Box 89, Folder 5)
- UTU National Agreement- 1972 (Box 89, Folder 6)
- The Conrail Inside Track (Box 89, Folder 7)
- Guide to Employee Stock Ownership Plans (Box 89, Folder 8)
  Minor Damage due to adhesion with another source
- Carrier Sec. 6 Notices, 1977 (Box 89, Folder 9)
- United States Court of Appeals for the Third Circuit (Box 89, Folder 10)
- Handling of Rail Disputes Under the Railway Labor Act, 1950-69, 1950-1969 (Box 89, Folder 11)
- Keeping America Moving: New Transportation Concepts for a New Century (Box 89, Folder 12)
- A New Approach to the Nation's Transportation Problems (Box 89, Folder 13)
- Association of American railroads Research and Test Department (Box 89, Folder 14)
- Preliminary/Final System Plan (Box 89, Folder 15)
- Misc. Correspondence (Box 89, Folder 16)
- Agreements and Decisions (Box 89, Folder 17)
- News and Developments (Box 89, Folder 18)
- Award Circulars (Box 89, Folder 19)
- Drugs/ Alcohol (Box 89, Folder 20)
- "Getting a Message to Congress" (Box 89, Folder 21)
- How Long Will You be Just One of the Boys? (Box 89, Folder 22)
- News/ Developments (Box 89, Folder 23)
- Labor/ Management Cooperation in Multicarrier Rail Terminals (Box 89, Folder 24)
- 1989 Directory (Box 89, Folder 25)
- Project REAP: A Report to the Industry, 1980 (Box 89, Folder 26)
- Report of the Board of Trustees of the United Transportation Union, 1971 (Box 89, Folder 27)
- "Background" Vol. 22 (Box 89, Folder 28)
- News Clippings (Box 90, Folder 1)
- Harbridge House Inc. (Box 90, Folder 2)
- DOT on Northeast (Box 90, Folder 3)
- "Railroad Industry Review-1972" (Box 90, Folder 4)
- Fees for Arbitration Cases (Box 90, Folder 5)
- Penn- Central Trustees, 1973 (Box 90, Folder 6)
- Letter to Forbes Magazine (Box 90, Folder 7)
- Welcome to Your Union (Box 90, Folder 8)
- United Farm Workers vs Teamster (Box 90, Folder 9)
- "Yearbook of Railroad Facts: 1969-1989," Missing 1972-1975 (Box 90, Folder 10)
- "The Train-Watcher's Guide to North American Railroads" (Box 90, Folder 11)
- "Your Labor Union" (Box 90, Folder 12)
- The Constitution of the United States of America (Box 90, Folder 13)
- Constitution ad Statutes Rules of Order, 1966 (Box 90, Folder 14)
- Constitution of the. Of L.F.&E. 1963 (Box 90, Folder 15)
- Technical Assistance to the Reap Study Railroads (Box 90, Folder 16)
- "Background" Vol. 22 (Box 90, Folder 17)
- Central Labor Rehabilitation Council of New York, Inc. (Box 90, Folder 18)
- Report of the Controller of the United Transportation Union Insurance Association, 1976 (Box 90, Folder 19)
- Audited Financial Statements and Other Financial Information (Box 90, Folder 20)
- UTUIA- Bd. Of Directors Meeting and Minutes, 1971-1973 (Box 90, Folder 21)
- Audited Financial Statements and Other Financial Information (Box 90, Folder 22)
- UTU Member Book (Box 90, Folder 23)
- GCA- 1988 (Box 90, Folder 24)
- Drunk Driving (Box 90, Folder 25)
- Report of the National Association of Insurance Commissioners (Box 90, Folder 26)
- Report of the Controller of the United Transportation Union Insurance Association (Box 90, Folder 27)
- United States Court of Appeals for the Third Circuit- No. 90-1436 (Box 90, Folder 28)
- The Federal Budget Analysis and Review (Box 90, Folder 29)
- Report of the Controller of the UTU Insurance Association (Box 90, Folder 30)
- Agreements (Box 90, Folder 31)
- Drugs and Alcohol (Box 90, Folder 32)
- Misc. Correspondence (Box 90, Folder 33)
- News/Developments (Box 90, Folder 34)
- Employee Assistance Program Workshop- Instructor Manual (Box 90, Folder 35)
- UTU Grievance Handling by Rail Local Chairpersons (Box 90, Folder 36)
- (Box 90, Folder 37)
- "Background" Vol. 16-19 (Box 91, Folder 1)
- "Background" Vol. 22-23 (Box 91, Folder 2)
- "Background" Vol. 14 (Box 91, Folder 3)
- Award Circulars (Box 91, Folder 4)
- "Background" Vol. 6 and Vol. 13 (Box 91, Folder 5)
- "Options for Conrail" (Box 91, Folder 6)
- Employee Protection (Box 91, Folder 7)
- Sixteenth Progress Report on the St. Louis Project (Final Report) (Box 91, Folder 8)
- North Dakota Short Line (Box 91, Folder 9)
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers Correspondence (Box 91, Folder 10)
- Eligibility for Office (Box 91, Folder 11)
- News Clippings (Box 91, Folder 12)
- Chicago and Northwestern (Box 91, Folder 13)
- Houston Belt and Terminal Railway Co. (Box 91, Folder 14)
- Misc. Correspondence (Box 91, Folder 15)
- Springfield Terminal Railway Co. (Box 91, Folder 16)
- Metro- North Commuter Railroad (Box 91, Folder 17)
- Conrail (Box 91, Folder 18)
- CSX (Box 91, Folder 19)
- "Nickel Plate Road" (Box 91, Folder 20)
- Hi Speed Rails (Box 91, Folder 21)
- Coal Slurry (Box 91, Folder 22)
- The Doorway to Better Things (Box 91, Folder 23)
- The Nationwide Experience with New Small Railroads Formed to Take Over Abandoned Lines 1971-1984 (Box 92, Folder 1)
- The Experience in Five Midwest States with New Short Line Railroads Formed to Take Over Lines Abandoned by Major Systems (Box 92, Folder 2)
- University Research Corp. Phase II Alcohol Study (Box 92, Folder 3)
- "Railroad Transportation and Public Policy" (Box 92, Folder 4)
- Report of General Secretary and Treasurer- 1988 (Box 92, Folder 5)
- "How to be a More Effective Union Representative" (Box 92, Folder 6)
- "Supervisors' Handbook" (Box 92, Folder 7)
- "Supervisors' Handbook" (Box 92, Folder 8)
- Milwaukee Road (Box 92, Folder 9)
- Milwaukee Road 1982 (Box 92, Folder 10)
- 1978 Aug-Sept 79 (Box 92, Folder 11)
- Roch Inland 1974-1975 (Box 92, Folder 12)
- Jan. 80 (Box 92, Folder 13)
- Milwaukee- Stock Plan (Box 92, Folder 14)
- Milwaukee Road (Box 92, Folder 15)
- Nov. 79 (Box 92, Folder 16)
- Dec. 79 (Box 92, Folder 17)
- Oct. 79 (Box 92, Folder 18)
- Feb. 80 (Box 92, Folder 19)
- Mar. 80 (Box 92, Folder 20)
- Apr. 80 (Box 92, Folder 21)
- Reports and News (Box 92, Folder 22)
- Labor/Management Cooperation at Conrail (Box 92, Folder 23)
- Employee Assistance Programs (Box 92, Folder 24)
- Map (Box 92, Folder 25)
- FRA Drug and Alcohol Policies (Box 93, Folder 1)
- BLE-CNW (Box 93, Folder 2)
- Chicago Seminar (Box 93, Folder 3)
- Milw. 1893 (Box 93, Folder 4)
- Wage and Rules- 1981 (Box 93, Folder 5)
- "Uniform Code of Operating Rules" (Box 93, Folder 6)
- Constitution and Statues Rule of Order and Laws Governing the Mutual Benefit Department and Accident Insurance Department- Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen, 1966 (Box 93, Folder 7)
- Rail Restructuring- Midwest (Box 93, Folder 8)
- A Proposal for Tasks I and II Submitted to: Houston Terminal Project (Box 93, Folder 9)
- SEPTA (Box 93, Folder 10)
- Labor- Management (Box 93, Folder 11)
- ASTRO (Box 93, Folder 12)
- Short Lines (Box 93, Folder 13)
- Coordination and Consolidation of Freight Services in the Northern New Jersey Area (Box 93, Folder 14)
- Coordination and Consolidation of Freight Services in the Northern New Jersey Area (Box 93, Folder 15)
- Development of a National Railroad Labor Management Training Program (Box 93, Folder 16)
- BLE C+NW (Box 93, Folder 17)
- Conrail Labor-Management (Box 93, Folder 18)
- "Background" Vol. 19 (Box 93, Folder 19)
- "Background" Vol. 22 (Box 93, Folder 20)
- "A Program of Experiments Involving Changes in Terminal Operations- 1974 Progress Report" (Box 93, Folder 21)
- Bypass Agreements (Box 93, Folder 22)
- United Transportation Union Research and Schedule Department Directory (Box 93, Folder 23)
- Drugs and Alcohol (Box 93, Folder 24)
- The Pennsylvania Railroad Company (Box 93, Folder 25)
- Report on CIV Railroad Worker Training (Box 93, Folder 26)
- "A Rail Perspective" (Box 93, Folder 27)
- "What Every Member Should Know About Federal Railroad Safety Laws and Regulations- 1984" (Box 93, Folder 28)
- "Your Labor Union" (Box 93, Folder 29)
- Section I: Summary Evaluation and Recommendations, The Milwaukee Road Quality Circle Project, 1981-1983 (Box 94, Folder 1)
- EAP Activity Report, 1972-1986 (Box 94, Folder 2)
- EAP Activity Report, 1972-1988 (Box 94, Folder 3)
- Proceedings of the 1980 Conference, Project REAP: A Report to the Industry (Box 94, Folder 4)
- "Your Future Demands Decisions Based on Facts. You Deserve all the Answers!" (Box 94, Folder 5)
- Operation Redblock: First Annual Conference (Box 94, Folder 6)
- Midmonth Employment for Class I Railroads (Box 94, Folder 7)
- Proposal for a Program of Experiments Involving Change in Operations in the Kansas City Gateway, 1980 (Box 94, Folder 8)
- Ohio Dept.- Insurance- Report of Examination of UTUIA (Box 94, Folder 9)
- Fringe Benefits- RR Employees, 1975 (Box 94, Folder 10)
- A Guide to Employee Assistance Programs (Box 94, Folder 11)
- "A Cooperative Program of Experiments Involving Changes in Railroad Operations" (Box 94, Folder 12)
- Instructor Training Manual (Box 94, Folder 13)
- A Guide to Help You Put Out Your Own Newsletter (Box 94, Folder 14)
- Operation Redblock Work Book (Box 94, Folder 15)
- "Background" Vol. 22-23 (Box 94, Folder 16)
- Arbitration Proceedings (Box 94, Folder 17)
- Emergency Board Reports (Box 94, Folder 18)
- Misc. Correspondence (Box 94, Folder 19)
- Newsletters (Box 94, Folder 20)
- Employee Assistance Program (Box 94, Folder 21)
- "Era of Giants: The New Railroad Merger Movement" (Box 94, Folder 22)
- Norfolk Southern Operating Rules (Box 94, Folder 23)
- (Box 94, Folder 24)
- Statement and Determination Mediators (Box 95, Folder 1)
- Changes in Representation- Unification Document (Box 95, Folder 2)
- Correspondence- "Trainmen" Locals (Box 95, Folder 3)
- Correspondence- Relating to 4 Way Unification Plans (Box 95, Folder 4)
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen (Box 95, Folder 5)
- National Mediation Bd. Certification UTU (Box 95, Folder 6)
- Merger Proposal- BRAC-TCU-1968 (Box 95, Folder 7)
- DWC (Box 95, Folder 8)
- BRAC- Proposal with ORC-B (Box 95, Folder 9)
- Unification Correspondence (Box 95, Folder 10)
- National Labor Relations Board Certification (Box 95, Folder 11)
- Amendment Proposals (Box 95, Folder 12)
- Membership Data- SUNA-ORC+B-BLF+E (Box 95, Folder 13)
- Milwaukee Railroad Task Force (Box 95, Folder 14)
- Restructuring Task Force (Box 95, Folder 15)
- Task Force, 1976 (Box 95, Folder 16)
- Chicago Terminal (Box 95, Folder 17)
- Terminal Task Force Progress Reports, 1975 (Box 95, Folder 18)
- St. Louis Terminal Project Schedule and Progress Reports (Box 95, Folder 19)
- Task Force on Rail Transportation Meeting, 1976 (Box 95, Folder 20)
- Evaluation of Changes in Terminal Operations, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 21)
- Terminal Task Force Meeting, 1975 (Box 95, Folder 22)
- Terminal Task Force Meeting, 1975 (Box 95, Folder 23)
- Proposed 1976 Contract (Box 95, Folder 24)
- Evaluation of Changes in Terminal Operations (Box 95, Folder 25)
- Trends and Statistics (Box 95, Folder 26)
- P-C System Committee (Box 95, Folder 27)
- NCA Labor-Management Meeting Statler-Hilton Hotel, 1975 (Box 95, Folder 28)
- Intermodal Project (Box 95, Folder 29)
- Intermodal Operational Test and Evaluation (Box 95, Folder 30)
- Task Force Midwest and Conference (Box 95, Folder 31)
- PBC "Annual Report" (Box 95, Folder 32)
- (Box 95, Folder 33)
- "Wage and Rules- 1981" Vol. I (Box 96, Folder 1)
- "Wage and Rules- 1981" Vol. II (Box 96, Folder 2)
- "Wage and Rules- 1981" Vol. III (Box 96, Folder 3)
- "Wage and Rules- 1981" Vol. IV (Box 96, Folder 4)
- "Wage and Rules- 1981" Vol. V (Box 96, Folder 5)
- State of Ohio High Speed Rail Task Force (Box 96, Folder 6)